HEY
來
These days...
面具，在這個世界上
Almost everyone is wearing a mask
幾乎每一個人都戴著一張面具
Kind ones, ugly ones
有善良的，也有醜惡的
in all walks of society
在各式各樣的社會環境中
Getting what they need
博取生活的所需
We hope that some day...
我們希望有一天
we wouldn't need to wear masks anymore
大家都沒有面具
We can just be our true selves
還我本來的面目
Even if masks are necessary
即使必要的話
I hope it'd just be the docile kind,
you know
也是一張善良的面具
Du Pi Personnel Agency
Looking for a job?
應徵的?
Yes
是
If you could please fill this out
把這個填上
Sure
好
It's done
填好了
Call in the blue-jacket guy first
叫那個穿藍夾克的先進來
Sure, Miss Du asks you in
好的，杜小姐叫你進去
Miss Du?
杜小姐?
She's our boss
是我們的老闆
Come in
進來
Lin Weibin?
林偉彬?
Yes
是
You're new to the city?
剛從外地來不久?
Yes
是
You've got quite a good stature,
take off your clothes
外型不錯，把上衣給脫了
Sorry?
什麼?
Done
脫了
Fine, take off your pants
很好，把褲子也脫了
What do you mean, Miss Du?
杜小姐，這是什麼意思?
Just to look at your figure
看看你的身材
Do all the interviewees
是不是所有來找工作的人
have to take off their clothes?
都要脫衣服?
If you want a job
如果你真的要找工作
Then just do as told
就聽我的話去做
You don't need me to take off my pants
難道看一個人的身材
...in order to look at my figure
一定要脫褲子?
I'll explain later
我會解釋的
And your underwear
底褲
What?
什麼?
It's off
脫了
Fine, you may dress up now
好，把衣服穿上吧
What kind of job is it anyway?
這是什麼工作?
I've got a job for you
我決定給你一份事情
It's a proper job
這不是什麼不正當的職業
It's a swimwear modeling job
是去替一間公司做模特兒
for a company
Modeling? Never done it before, you see
示範泳裝
示範?我從來沒試過
It's easy, just wear their swimwear
很容易，只要穿了他們的泳裝
and you'll be in a photo shoot
拍幾張照片就行了
That's why I had to first lookout
所以我一定要看看你的身上
for any scars on your body
有沒有疤痕
Well, do you want the job or not?
你願意嗎?
Yes, I do
願意
Please sign here
你同意就簽個字吧
It's a good temp job
拍幾張照，賺幾百塊錢也不錯
Thank you
謝謝你
Come here at 101a.m. tomorrow
好，明天上午十點你到這兒來
I'll take you there
我帶你一起去
Miss Du
杜小姐
Salsali, this is Mr. Lin Weibin
莎莎麗，這位是林偉彬先塹
Salsali is the top model in town
莎莎麗是本地最著名的模特兒
Go get changed
一塊去換衣服去
Who's he? Where's David?
他?大偉呢?
He's busy
他今天沒有空
I've told you before
我早說過
I want to pick my partner for the shoot
跟我一起拍照的人我要選過的
Mr. Lin is very experienced
林先生很有經驗的
Never mind
算了
The photographer is waiting, hurry
攝影師在等，叫他快點換衣服
Where do I change?
我在什麼地方換衣服?
Mr. Lin
林先生
If you're an experienced model
如果你是一個有經驗的模特兒
You shouldn't have a problem
getting changed here
你應該知道在女人面前換衣服
It's no big deal
根本不算是一件什麼大不了的事
Hurry, we are waiting
快點，別讓人家等
I charge HK$150 an hour
我是一百五十元一小時的
You've got a good physique
你身材還不錯
What kind of pose is this?
你這叫什麼姿勢?
Help him to strike a pose, Salsali
莎莎麗，你就替他擺個姿勢吧
That's it
好了
How long was the shoot?
一共拍了多少時間?
2 hours 15 minutes
兩小時十五分
Charge as a hours
以三小時計算
Sure
好
lean? believe you found him
to be my partner
找一個這樣的人來跟我搭檔
I know the pictures won't turn out well
這個照片一定拍不好
I know
我知道
I'll find Mr. Huang for your fees
我去找黃經理跟你們拿錢去
This is your first shoot, right?
你這是第一次吧
Why did Du Pi believe you?
為什麼杜琵聽你瞎吹
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字?
Lin Weibin
林偉彬
Good stature, lacks experience
你身材還不錯，就是沒有經驗
not nimble enough,
weak sensitization to lighting
不靈活，感光慢
What sensitization?
感光慢?
You're too dumb to be a model
笨，這樣笨還想做模特兒
Don't look down on me,
I'm just doing this for the
你不要瞧不起我，要不是為了生活
money, otherwise, I wouldn't be here
我絕不會到這個地方，跟你拍照的
Why did you come here then?
那你為什麼要來做模特兒?
I never planned to be a model
管你什麼模不模的
well whatever, none of my concern
你愛怎麼樣模，與我都無關
Let me tell you
告訴你
You are very rude
你連做人的普通禮貌都不懂
I thought you've been trained
我剛才以為你是受過訓練臥
And you were so clumsy, that's why
看著你這樣笨拙，我才會
sorry
對不起
If you're looking for work
如果你要找工作
You can gel some training in this field
你可以參加做模特兒的訓練
I've weak sensitization to lighting
我感光太慢
That's 'cause you haven't been trained
那是因為你沒有受過訓練
Take this card
拿去
Drop by if you are free
你有空就來吧
My Place
我的家
Take a seat
坐呀
Sit Down
坐下來嘛
This is your pay
這是你的酬勞
I gave you the best rate
按照最高的價錢給你
HK$450 in total
四百五十塊
Thank you
謝謝你
I should give you back 10%
我應該抽十分之一給你
That's alright, you don't need to
不必了，你不必用錢來謝我
Miss Du
杜小姐
Those were taken when I was younger
都是我的照片
They're great
拍得很好
These were taken
by my earlier photographer
那是我以前的攝影師照的
Are you a virgin?
有過女人沒有?
C'mon, don't be shy
不用害臊
It's a physiological need,
nothing great!
這是生理的需要，很普通的一回事
Are You?
有過嗎?
No, I used to see a Malaysian girl
一個馬來西亞的女孩子
Do you love her?
你愛她?
Or course,
otherwise I wouldn't have slept with her
不愛她，怎麼能發生關係呢?
Is she here with you?
你沒有把她帶來?
I can't even take care of myself
我連自己都養不活
My glorious days are over
一切都過去了
I was once pretty; had lots of boyfriends
我曾經美麗過，也吸引過不少男人
I am not young anymore
可是歲月不饒人
Do you think I'm old?
我老了嗎?
Not at all
沒有
I keep myself busy all day
白天我整天在忙碌著
My career keeps me going
用事業可以滿足我
But when I'm home
可是一回到家裏
I have time to think about things
就什麼都想起來了
You really don't know what I mean?
你真的不懂我的意思?
I ---
我…
Let's go into the room
到房裏去
Thanks
好，謝謝
Wait
站住
You sneak into your room everyday
你每天偷偷地溜進房去
You still haven't paid your rent
房錢呢?
Here's HK$400, I've paid it Off
四百塊，清帳了
What? You struck gold?
怎麼發財了
None of your business
那是我的事，與你無關
I want to talk to you in my rooto
到我房裏頭去，我有話要跟你說
Come here
來呀
What is it?
有什麼?事?快點說
Sit
坐呀
You know, with all this inflation...
現在物價飛漲，房租也不例外
lam going to charge you more
所以我要加你的房錢
HK$300 more per month, HK$10 per day
每天加十塊，一個月三百塊
No way, I can't afford it
對不起，我付不起
I can move out right away
我可以立刻搬走
Since I've already paid up
反正房租已經付清了
You think I'm giving you a hard time?
那我就很為難了
There's a guesthouse next door
也好，我們隔壁有一家招待所
They charge HK$12 more a day
你不妨去問問他們，每天漲十二塊
Plenty of people
are looking for places to stay
現在寸金尺土，你不住有人住
Could you be a bit more reasonable?
能不能少一點?
You're single without a steady job
你單身一個男人又沒份固定的職業
I'm doing you a favor
我是同情你
And you've been a good tenant
而且你做人又規矩
You never bring any girls here
從來不帶什麼?女人回來過夜
So are you not interested in women?
怎麼…你不喜歡女人嗎?
What?
什麼?
I mean, there're many sick guys around
世界上變態的人太多
I have seen them all
我什麼人沒見過?
Two men renting a room from time to time
有時候兩個大男人上來開房
You aren't one of those, are you?
你不是這種人吧?
Of course not
少胡說
Come here
你過來嘛
I know you're not one of them
我知道你不會是那種兔子
Not interested?
對我有沒有興趣?
Then I'll have to charge you more rent
這麼說我非加你房錢不可了
Are you saying that
if I'm interested in you
如果我對你有興趣
then you won't charge me more?
你就不加我房租?
Deal
好，我願意
Take it all off
再脫
Come here
過來呀
I'd rather sleep on the streets
你找錯對象，我寧願睡在馬路土
than to sleep with you
也不碰你這種爛女人
Damn it, listen
他媽的，你聽著
10 Dollars more per day
從今天起每天加十塊
Not a penny less
一毛也不能少
Otherwise gel the hell out
要不然你馬上給我滾蛋
(Our job openings have been filled)
本公司聘請文員
thuman Resources Department
已告額滿，人事部啟
Good, next one
很好，下一位
Keep going, turn
往前走，轉圈
A bit slower, hands on waist, turn
慢一點，兩手叉腰，轉圈
Watch your pose when going in
注意進去的姿勢
Very good
很好
Alright, this is the end of class today
各位我們今天時間到了
We'll continue practice next time. Bye
後天再練吧，拜拜
Bye
拜拜
What a surprise to see you!
想不到你會來
I was nearby
我在下面找事情
Then I saw the sign of your company
看見你的招牌進來看看
Still looking for work?
還在找事
They've already hired
運氣不好，已經有了人
Take it easy
慢慢再等機會
I guess I don't have a choice
也只好這樣了
This is for the fashion show?
這是時裝表演用的台?
Yes, it's called the 'ramp'
對了，這就叫做走台
They say it isn't easy to tread on it
在上面走不容易
To be a model one has to go through a to:
做模特兒也不是容易捱的
For now, we lack male models
目前時裝界男性模特兒很缺乏
with a stature like you
像你這樣的身材很少
You said I was dumb
你說過我太笨了
I'll train you
有機會我好好教你
I can't afford the tuition
這麼貴的學費我交不趕
Friends are supposed to help each other
有時候朋友之間是不應該講錢的
Right then, I'm packing up
好了，我要關門了
Let's eat lunch together
我們去吃點東西
I'm gonna go for a set-lunch
我要一個午餐
What about you?
你呢?
Just a coffee
我要一杯咖啡
Have you eaten?
你吃過年餐了?
Don't worry, my treat. Two sets please
沒關係，我請你，兩個
Right away
是
Financial considerations, right?
你的環境真的這麼困難?
You alone in town here?
你一個人在這裏呀?
My family's back home
他們都在家鄉
Life's difficult there,
that's why I came here
因為生活困難，所以我一個人來
Because I thought it'd be easier
in the city
我以為在大城市總此小地方好
Who knew...
誰知道…
I understand
我瞭解你的心情
Or else you wouldn't have claimed to be...
不然你也不會冒充第一流的模特兒
a mp model and worked
in the shoot with me
跟我一起拍照
I didn't lie, it was Du Pi
我沒有冒充，是杜琵…
She helped you out a great deal
她確實幫了你一個大忙
I never work with inexperienced models
我是不跟沒有名氣的模特兒
Just the mp professionals
混在一起的
You're a tad haughty
你好像很驕傲
That I am
我承認
But I am the best in town
在這兒我是首屈一指的
That's why the airs
有了這種名氣，我必須驕傲
How did you get where you are today?
你是怎麼爬上去的?
Call it - Luck,
opportunities and qualifications
運氣、機會和本身的條件
I believe it's mostly my survival skills
最重要的是靠自己的手腕
Survival skills?
手腕?
It's not easy to climb up
告訴你，要爬上去並不容易
But it's even harder to stay on mp
要保持在上面更難，你一定明白
Fame is good, money is good
名氣是好的，金錢更是好的
When all the efforts
and hard work pays off
當你花的心血得到這些
It's worth it
以前受的苦你就不在乎
Yeah
是的
Don't worry, I'll think of something
你放心，我替你想想辦法
If there's any job in fashion
如果在時裝界有什麼?工作
I'll let you know
我告訴你
Thanks
謝謝你
Hello, who are you looking for?
喂，找誰呀?
Hold on
等等
Damn,
what's with all the women calling him?
他媽的，女人的電話倒不少
Hey, you have a call
姓林的，電話
Hello
喂
This is Du Pi
我是杜琵
Weibin, I've found you a job
偉彬，我替你找了一份工作
Really?
真的?
Come over right away, wear a suit
馬上來，記住，穿西裝打領帶
You got enough for a cab fare?
有車錢嗎?
Yes
有…
Good, get here soon, hurry
好，坐的士來，越快越好
Why aren't you still dressed?
怎麼還不穿衣服?
Close the door, the maid's outside
把門關上，別給傭人看到
Come here
來呀
I asked you to hurry
coz I don't like to wait
我要你趕來，是因為我不喜歡等人
Do you miss me?
幾天不見了，你想我嗎?
Don't make my clothes wrinkle
別把衣服弄皺了
Take them off
脫掉它
ls this the job you told me about?
你替我找的工作就是這一份嗎?
Behave!
正經點
Give it to me, I'to yours
給我，我是你的
I'm all yours
我整個人是你的
You're really strange 1
你真是一個奇怪的人
At the office, you're very professional
在公司裏，你一本正經
But once at home
可是回到家裏…
This is human nature
這就是人
I unmask at home
真人面前自然要把面具除掉
Unmask?
面具?
Yes, we're all wearing masks
面具，每個人都戴著它
So that we can hide behind them
戴了它可以把自己藏起來
Not revealing our true selves
讓別人永遠猜不透摸不著
Especially women
尤其是女人
Right, I better wear a mask myself
對，我也要把面具戴起來
So that people can't figure me out
讓別人永遠猜不透我
Silly boy, men aren't good at pretending
傻小子，男人是不菩於偽裝的
Especially you
尤其是你
You are an open book
心裏想什麼，一看就知道
Come here, and forget about work
過來，別想工作的事
Let's do it
and then I'll take you over later
先給我，待會兒我帶你去
Please have a seat
請坐
Thank you
Sorry we're late, Mrs. Ou
歐太太，對不起，讓你久等了
What's your name?
你叫什麼?名字?
Lin Weibin
林偉彬
Are you working?
沒有其他的工作吧?
No
沒有
Can you start right away?
你能立刻上工嗎?
Yes
可以
Good
很好
You know what the job is?
你知道是什麼工作了吧?
You haven't told him?
你沒有跟他說?
I want you to meet him first
我想先帶來給您看看
I'll (ell him about the job later
看中了我才向他說
Is he trustworthy?
他靠得住嗎
I can assure you, he's honest,
hardworking
我可以擔保他誠實勤勞
and healthy
而且身體也好
Fine, I'll pay you HK$700 a month for now
好吧，我先付你七百塊錢一個月
If I'm happy with your work
如果你做得好
Then I'll give you a raise each month
我會按月加你的薪冰
A raise each month?
按月加薪
But this is a live-in job
不過一定要住在這兒
No problem
是，你放心
I'll do a good job
這份工作我一定能做
Alright then, you start tomorrow morning
好吧，你明天一早來上工
Are you married?
你結婚沒有?
No
沒有
Girlfriend?
那麼…女朋友呢?
No
也沒有
Why not?
為什麼?
I can't even take care of myself
自己也養不活，別的根本談不到
You're here on your own
你一個人到這裏來謀生活
You must be lonely
一定很寂寞
Be honest, what's the relationship
你不要瞞我，介紹你來的杜小姐
between you and Miss Du?
跟你是什麼關係?
Just friends
只是朋友
What kind of friends?
什麼朋友
Mrs. Ou, why are you asking me this?
歐太太，你為什麼要這樣問呢?
I've mm you, I like honest men
我說過，我喜歡坦白的人
We
我們…
I know there's more to it than appears
你不說，我早就看出來了
I was under pressure, Mrs. Ou
這是迫不得已的，歐太大
For work, I had to entertain her
為了工作，我非應付她不可
How many times?
多少次?
Mrs. Ou
歐太太
Shameless woman
這不要臉的女人
A widow, seducing men with her power
一個寡婦，利用職權勾引男人
Stay away from her
你不要再跟她來往了
You've got a job now
你現在已經有了工作
Lodge and board, you don't need her now
吃和住都有了，不必再應付她
Yes ma'am
是
And stay away from other girls
也不要跟別的女孩子來往
Other girls?
別的女孩子?
I like a clean marl
我要一個乾乾淨淨的男人
Mrs. Ou, I'to going back to my rooto
歐太太，我回房去了
If you need anything,
ring the bell for me
有什麼事，按鈐叫我
Hold on
等一等
Prepare the bath for me
到浴室去，替我放滿了溫水
And put the bath salts in
把浴粉也放下去
Yes madam
是
Mrs. Ou, the bath's ready
歐太太，水放好了
Close the door
把房門關上
Switch off the light
把燈關了
Mrs. Ou
歐太太
Switch it off
關掉
Come here
你過來
My legs are such a drag
這要命的腿
Come here
過來
Take them off for me
幫我脫了
Mrs. Ou, I
歐太太，這…
What?
怎麼了?
Carry me in
抱我進去
Hurry
快點
Take off the clothes
把衣服脫了
What are you afraid of?
怕什麼?呢
Mrs. Ou
歐太太…
I am payin'you, you better listen to me
我花錢顧你，你什麼?都得聽我的
Mrs. Ou, I
歐太太，這…
Mr. Lin, there's a lady looking for you
林先生，有人找你，是位小姐
Salsali
莎莎麗
Didn't expect me here, did ya ?
想不到是我吧
How do you know I live here?
你怎麼知道我住在這兒?
I went to that place you stayed at
我到你住的地方去找你
The lady boss was rude,
she said you moved out
那老闆娘好兇，說你搬了
And then you asked Du Pi?
你去問杜琵?
She wouldn't (ell me
杜琵不肯告訴我
However, her secretary did
是她女秘書告訴我的
Are you free?
能出去嗎
It's my day off, I'm bored
今天我放假，已經悶了一天了
Let's go
走呀
Fine, I'll grab my jacket
好，我去拿件衣服
Have a seat
請坐
What would you like to drink?
喝點什麼?
Mint drink, what about you?
一杯薄荷酒，你呢?
Coke
可樂
Give him whisky
給他威士忌
Right away
好
I don't drink
我不會喝酒
A little drink and smoke won't hurt
抽抽煙，喝喝酒，這才像男人
This is the most expensive club in town
這是此地最貴的夜總會
Why are we in such a place?
到這麼貴的地方來幹什麼?
I wanna introduce you
to some industry contacts
帶你見見幾位時裝界的朋友
There she is
在那兒
Let me introduce
來，我來介紹一下
This is Lin Weibin, he's new in town
這是外地來的林偉彬
Linda
琳達
David
大偉
Angela
安琪拉
Raymond
雷蒙
Take a seat
坐
What would you like to have?
各位喝點什麼?
Brandy... Neat
我要純白蘭地
And you, sir?
這位呢?
The same
一樣
What about you?
那位?
Scotch whisky
蘇格蘭威士忌
Since when are you
with such a dashing boyfriend?
什麼時候找來的這麼英俊男朋友
I've only known him for a few days
才認識幾天
I thought he's one of your students
我還以為是你的學生
I want to train him,
he's got quite a good frame
我真的想訓練他，他的體型很不錯
Let's go dancing
我們跳舞去
I don't know how to dance
我不會
It's just an exercise
就當是腹部運動
I really can't manage
我真的不會
Come, I'll dance with you
來，我來跟你跳
Sure
好
Let's go dancing
我們跳舞去吧
Sure
好
You just shake it through
這種舞只要亂扭亂擺就行了
I don't know how
我不會扭也不會擺
Don't worry, come here
那我們就跳不扭不擺的，來嘛
Linda, dancing is not my thing
琳達小姐，這個樣子我會很窘的
What are you afraid of?
沒關係，怕什麼?
I thought David's your boyfriend
那個大偉是你的朋友嗎?
Boy, he's going to be cross!
他會生氣的
Never mind him
不管他
Do you want it?
你要嗎?
What?
要什麼?
This
這個
Answer me
回答我
Let's not talk about it
我們不要談這個
I want to do it
我可以給你
Excuse me
對不起
Let's go back to our seats
我們回去坐好了
What are you laughing about?
你笑什麼?
Did Linda make a move on you?
琳達一定約了你
How do you know?
你怎麼知道的?
She's like that
to all the men she's interested in
她對她所喜歡的男人都是這樣的
Does David know?
大偉知不知道?
David loves her like crazy
大偉愛她愛得都發狂呢
What have you told her?
你答應她了?
Laurel is about to come on stage
盧倫就要出場了
He's the most popular singer here
他是此地最受歡迎的歌星
I've given you my heart
此心我已給了你
And you'll have my heart forever
願意就讓它跟著你
Dump my heart if you don't accept my love
不願就把它拋棄
mm he great?
美不美?
I love to hear him sing
我喜歡聽他的歌
Pretty, like a girl
很漂亮，像個女孩子
I've given you my heart
此心我已給了你
Please keep it close
if you accept my love
接受就讓它伴著你
I won't blame you for forgetting me
忘掉它也不怨你
This is your right
這是你的權利
There's no future
過去歲月沒有追憶
There's no past
未來的日子沒有回憶
I've given you my clear life
空白的生命交給了你
My happiness or sorrow depends on you
是痛苦是甜蜜，全在你
I've given you my heart
此心我已給了你
And you'll have my heart forever
願意就讓它跟著你
Please don't dump it in the trash
不願就把它拋棄
I'll never hate you
我絕不怨恨你
Dump my heart if you don't accept my love
不願就把它拋棄
I'll never hate you
我絕不怨恨你
Salsali, good to see you
莎莎麗，你來了
Sit, let me introduce
坐，我來介紹
This is Laurel, this is Lin Weibin
這是名歌星盧倫，這是林偉彬
He's a model?
他也是模特兒?
He will be
他將來會是
I'to going to train hito
我已經決定收他做我的學生
What do you think of his frame?
你看他身材怎麼樣
He certainly could be an excellent model
他將來一定會成為一流的模特兒
Zhuzhu's singing is getting better
珠珠的歌越唱越好了
She's alright
哪裏
Zhuzhu is Laurel's girlfriend
珠珠就是盧倫的女朋友
Excuse me, I need to go on stage
對不起，我要上台去了
He's a good kid, smart and hard working
他是個好孩子，聰明勤土
But whenever the topic of
his girlfriend comes up
不過一提起他的女朋友
He runs away
他立刻就走掉
Why?
為什麼?
Cause he doesn't like girls
他不喜歡女孩子
Actually someone else
wanted to see you here
其實約你到這兒來的不是我
Who?
誰呀?
Linda
琳達
She asked me to arrange it
在夜總會化妝間裏她叫我約你來的
David was here earlier,
so it wasn't convenient
剛才大偉在不方便
Linda? What does she want with me?
琳達?她約我幹什麼?
You'll know later
待會兒你就知道
You two aren't swapping boyfriends,
I hope ?
你們是到這兒來交換男朋友?
No, I only date special men
不，我只跟特殊的男人
You choose your own lifestyle
其實各人有各人的生淮
You agree?
你說對嗎
Salsali
莎莎麗
I had to run away from David
真是的，好不容易才逃掉
Great, he's all yours
好了，人約來了
Bye
再見
Your place?
你有地方嗎?
I ---
我…
Come on, it'll be furl
好玩嘛
You
你…
lean? take you to my place
我的地方不能去
David will show up any time
大偉會隨時上去找我
You think this is a game?
你把這種事情當成兒戲了
Come on, what century are you from?
什麼世紀了嘛，走呀
You dog!
你這個風流鬼
You two are shameless! And who are you?
一對狗男女，你是什麼人?
Stand still
你給我站住
You rotten marl
你這個爛傢伙
Gel out of here!
你滾
You lied to me
你…你騙我
You pretended to be all decent
你平常裝著一本正經，規規矩矩的
You mm me
you don't have a wife or girlfriend
你說過你沒有太太，沒有女朋友
I thought you were clean
我以為你是乾乾淨淨的
And you're fooling around
with women like her?
想不到你跟這種女人混在一起
And you two were in my husband's bed?
還在我丈夫的床上干
You dog!
你這個不要臉的狗東西
You're worse than me
有人此我還爛
You get out of my house!
你…你給我滾，你給我滾
Sit
坐
Has Linda got you in trouble?
是不是琳達給了你什麼麻煩?
I'm not working at Mrs. Oil's
我已經不在歐太太那邊干了
Have you seen Linda?
見過琳達沒有?
I didn't want to it's because of you
我根本沒有意思跟她…都是你…
She's just playing, she's got David
她只是玩玩，她有大偉
Aren't you jealous? A little bit?
怎麼，你一點都不妒忌?
Jealous of what?
妒忌什麼?
I'm your friend
我明明是你的朋友
And you introduced me to Linda
你把我介紹給琳達
She likes you
她喜歡你嘛
I don't gel it
我不明白你
You'll understand one day
總有一天你會明白的
You've got to find another job?
你現在生活怎麼樣解決?
Yes, I'm putting up at Du Pi's
for the mean time
正在找，暫時住在杜琵家裏
Any additional conditions?
她有沒有附帶的條件?
I know women like her
我很清楚她這種女人
She's alright, but she's too lonely
人不壞，只是太寂寞了
Remember to look for me tomorrow,
I'll take you
記著，明天來找我，我帶你去
Hi, Du Pi
杜琵
Who gave you a to?
誰送你回來的?
Salsali
莎莎麗
Salsali?
莎莎麗?
You went out with her?
你偷偷地跟她在一起
Why didn't you tell me?
為什麼不告訴我?
Don't worry, she isn't like you
你放心，她不像你
She isn't so casual
隨便跟男人上床
What? She isn't?
什麼?她不跟男人上床
What is so special about her?
她脫了褲子是什麼?
She's just a slut
還不是一個洞
Don't insult her
你少侮辱她
She's helping me to find a job
我找她只是想請她幫忙找工作
Find a job
找工作
Have you forgotten about me?
忘記我了?
Of course not
記得
Are you alone?
Where's Salsali and the others?
你一個人?莎莎麗他們呢?
Are you here to listen to my songs?
不是來捧我的場嗎?
Yes
是的
Thanks
謝謝
Why aren't you drinking?
你怎麼不喝酒?
I didn't drink at first,
but then I got into it
我起初也不會的，慢慢就慣了
You are too young to drink
你這麼年輕，不應該喝酒
I don't know
why everyone considers me a kid
奇怪，為什麼?人人以為我是小孩子
I'm in my 20s
我都二十多歲了
I heard you're looking for work
聽說你正在找工作
Have you found a job?
找到了沒有?
Still hunting;
Prepared to do just about anything
正在找，我什麼?都肯做
I can't starve anymore
我不能再挨餓了
I'm now living at a woman's house
我現在住在一個女人的家裏
I hope to move out soon
希望能立刻搬走
Do you hate women?
你討厭女人?
I like men
我喜歡男人
Cheers
來
Don't drink (00 much
別喝得太多了
I thought about you and I hoped that...
我想過你好多次
you'll come again, and here you are!
希望你會再來，果然你來了
Do you hate me?
你討厭我嗎?
A to: of people hate guys like me
很多人討厭我這種人
It's a personal choice
不會，各人有各人的生活
It's not their business
與別人無關的
Right, we can be friends
對，我們可以做朋友了?
If you're in trouble, I'll help you
如果你有困難，我一定盡量幫助你
Thanks
謝謝你
Wait for me, I'to going to sing for you
我上台去唱首歌給你聽，你等我
Weibin
偉彬
Salsali, come inside
莎莎麗，裏面坐
You just got up?
你才起來?
Are you surprised to see me here?
我來找你，你感到意外嗎?
There's a fashion show
at the hotel tomorrow
明天在酒店舉行的時裝表演
I've decided to let you participate
我決定讓你參加
I'll go get changed
我馬上去準備
Where's Du Pi?
杜琵呢?
The old lady sleeps like a pig
這老太婆睡得像死豬一樣
I'll wait for you in the car
我到車裏等你
Great, I'll be ready in a minute
好，我馬上就好
Du Pi
杜琵
Du Pi?
杜琵?
Om lady, huh ?
老太婆?
You piece of shit
你這混帳
I treat you well, and you dare insult me!
我親你養你，你還要罵我
I'to going to fight you
我跟你拼了
Stop it
住手
Go with her!
你走，你跟她去
And never come back
永遠不要給我回來
I won't
我會的
I've had enough of you
受的氣也受夠了
I'd rather be homeless than stay here
情願餓死也不會靠你吃飯
Be independent?
不靠我?
Really? Do you have the money?
吃的住的，哪來的?
Well I've done my pan
我又沒白吃你的
Don't ever come back if you step out
你要是出了這個彌鞋就不要再回來
You
你…
Aren't you going to to me go?
你不讓我走嗎?
I ---
不…
It's over between us
從今以後我跟你一刀兩斷
I it's your fault
我…這次是你氣我的
I never liked you
煩死了，我從來也沒喜歡過你
It's all my fault
都怪我不好
You can hit me or scold me
你可以打我，可以罵我
Please stay, please
我求求你留下來，留下來
Weibin
偉彬
These are fine
這件可以了
Wrap them up please
請把它包起來
Be careful, don't get the props wrong
要小心記住，衣服配件不要弄錯了
I know
我知道
You can take the clothes back
你可以把衣服帶回去
Bring to the hotel tomorrow
明天帶到愛麗絲酒店
The show is during lunch time
午飯時間表演
You can show up earlier,
and watch the catwalk
你可以早一點去，看看那邊的走台
I'll be there early
我一定早到的
Thanks
謝謝你
Let's go
走吧
I'll give you a to:
我先送你回家
What's wrong?
怎麼了?
I have no place to go to
我根本沒有家
I mean, I'm not...
我是說杜琵那兒
going back to Du Pi's
我不回去了
Why not?
為什麼?
We had a slight row
她罵我，我沒辦法
She doesn't want me to hang out with you
她不讓我跟你在一起
column take it anymore,
I had to move out
我實在受不了，我非搬走不可
Where would you go?
那你到哪兒去?
Do you have money?
有錢嗎?
I'll sleep in the park if I have to
就是睡在公園裏我也有辦法捱過去
I will never go back to her place
我絕不會回到她家裏
I'll see you at the hotel tomorrow
你走吧，明天我在酒店等你
Weibin
偉彬
Come
來
Come with me
跟我走
How's my cooking?
我的工夫怎麼樣?
Very good
好
Do you eat chicken a lot?
你經常吃雞?
Can have anything if one can afford it
有了錢就什麼都有了
All except one thing, I won't keep a man
就是有一樣東西我不要
no matter how rich I am
不管我有多少錢我也不會養男人
Don't get me wrong,
but even if you have millions,
你不要誤會，就是你有一萬萬
I won't take your money
我也不會要你養我
Had I really been into all that...
假如我要靠女人吃飯
I wouldn't have left Du Pi
也不必離開杜琵
I regret for what I've done before
我真後悔，做過幾件見不得人的事
But I would like to start
with a clean slate
但是我可以從頭做起
I'm not a useless marl
我並不是一個沒有志氣的人
Drink up
把酒喝了
You should rest
你該休息了
I'll show you the guest room
我帶你到客房去
I'm just opposite,
call me if you need anything
我在對面房，有什麼?事叫我好了
Salsali
莎莎麗
See you tomorrow
明天見
Don't, stop to
不能這樣，不要
I've changed my mind
我已經改變主意了
Weibin, you have to forget about...
偉彬，一切已經發生了
what happened between us
明天起你要忘了
Why?
為什麼?
Don't ask me that
不要問我理由
Salsali
莎莎麗
You must forget it
你一定要忘掉它
You
你…
The clothes are there, I'm off
衣服全在那兒，我走了
Where are you going next?
你決定住在什麼地方
I don't know; with the money I made
還不知道，現在賺了點錢
Maybe I'll rent a room somewhere
也許去找間公寓，租一個房間
I know you can't go back to Du Pi's
我知道你不能回杜琵那兒
But you really can't stay at my place
可是我那兒…你實在不能住
I know. Bye
我知道，再見
Lin Weibin
林偉彬
Laurel
盧倫
I saw you at the fashion show.
You were great
我來捧你的場，你表演得好極了
Thanks
謝謝你
You'll be a famous model
你將來一定會走紅的
Are you going home?
你現在回家嗎?
I don't have a home
我已經沒有家了
I thought you're staying at Du Pi's
你不是住在杜琵家的嗎?
we had a fight, I moved out yesterday
鬧翻了，昨天才搬出來
Where are you staying now?
搬到什麼?地方?
Don't know yet
還不一定
I hope to find a cheap place
希望找到一個便宜的地戶
Come, let's go to my place
走，到我家裏去看看
Please
請
Sit down
坐呀
Your place?
這是你的家?
It's not big,
but there's room for one more
地方不大，一個人住是夠了
You're welcome to stay here
你沒地方住，歡迎你住到這兒
I don't know
這…
Don't worry, we're friends
不要緊，朋友是應該互相幫助的
Thanks
謝謝你
Come
來
This is the bedroom
這是臥房
There's only one bed
雖然只有一張床
But we can share it
我們兩個可以睡在一起
I Don't think it'd be such a good idea
這…不太好吧
Why not?
為什麼?
Listen, I don't want to bother you
只是打擾了你，不好意思
You won't
不會的
I sing at night
我每天晚上要去唱歌
Make yourself at home
你把這兒當你自己的家
it doesn't matter
愛做什麼?就做什麼?好了
Well then
好
I'm glad you're staying here
你住在這兒我已經很高興了
I'm too lonely
我一個人實在太寂寞了
Maybe I should be frank with you
也許我應該聲明一下
You told me at the club the last time
上次在夜總會，你告訴過我
about yourself
關於你自己…
You must understand that...
你要知道
I'm not your type of man
You and me...
我跟你…
We're different
是不一樣的
What?
什麼?
What do you think of me?
你把我當做什麼人?
Do you think I've some motives ?
你以為我有什麼企圖?
I ---
我…
You look down on me
你根本看不起我，看不起我
No, please understand
我是一個心直口快的人
I speak what's on my mind
心裏有什麼話，就說出來
Since you look down on me,
you should leave
你既然看不起我，那你走好了
No, I won't leave like this
不，這樣我不會走
I'm not looking down on you
我不是看不起你，別誤會
I hate myself
我恨我自己
Why are you like this, Laurel?
盧倫，怎麼會這樣子的?
Don't ask
不要再說了
That devil
魔鬼，那個魔鬼
What devil?
魔鬼?
I met a guy named Richard years ago
很久以前，我遇到一個叫理察的
He used to come to the club everyday
他天天來聽我唱歌
And he asked me to join him for drinks
後來他約我喝酒
I didn't know about him
我並不知道他是那樣的人
Al that time I didn't believe in...
我那時候根本不相信
homosexuality
有同性戀這回事情
One day, he took me to his place
有一次，他帶我到他家裏去
He gave me a ring
他拿一個鑽戒給我
And he told him that I belonged to him
說我是屬於他的
I was drunk
當時我喝了很多酒
Then he started kissing me and
後來發現他把我吻…後來他…
I was shivering
當時我全身發抖
But he didn't say anything
可是他說沒有什麼
It's nice to be loved
有個人愛你總是好的
Laurel
盧倫
Then I thought of it as a sin
事後我深深的覺得這是一種罪惡
I swore I'll never see him again
我發誓永遠不再見他
But later
可是忽然間…
He seemed to have changed me
他好像改變了我
When I saw him again
當我再見到他的時候
I was happy
我是那麼的高興
Then I knew it's over for me
我知道我完了
Then he left me for good
從此他離開了我
Laurel, forget about him
盧倫，這是不正常的，忘掉他
I can't
不…我沒有辦法
Love your girlfriend
去愛你的女朋友
No, I can't
不，我不能，我沒有辦法
Laurel
盧倫
You can laugh at me
or despise me all you want
你笑我，罵我也好
I've mm you everything
我把一切都告訴了你
I've not told anyone before
我從來沒有告訴過別人
Don't be sad, I understand
不要難過，我瞭解你的心情
You're a good guy
你真是一個好人
Hello
喂
It's me, Weibin
我是偉彬
How do you know this number?
你怎麼知道我家電話
I found it, Salsali. I want to see you
查到的，莎莎麗，我想見見你
No, I'm busy
不，我有事
I want to see you right away,
I'to coming over
我一定要見你，我馬上到你家來
No, I've got a guest
不可以，我有客人
Then I'll meet you at the parking lot
in half an hour
那半小時以後，我在停車場等你
Hello ?
喂
Don't call my home next time
下次不要打電話到我家來
Why not?
為什麼?
Ir you need to talk to me, call my office
要有什麼公事打到儀態中心去
It's personal
我找你是私事
There's nothing personal between us
我與你之間沒有私事
You really have forgotten
about that night?
你真的忘了那個晚上?
Please forget it
請你忘了那件事
Haven't I told you before?
我不是跟你說過了嗎?
Why do you resent me?
你為什麼?對我這樣反感?
Forget it
忘了吧
I can't
我忘不了
I've met many women
我曾經遇見過許多女人
But you're different
可是，你是不同的
You asked me out just to tell me this?
你叫我出來就是為了這個?
I just want you to know
我要讓你知道
Weibin
偉彬
You must understand
你要明白
we can never be together
我們永遠不能夠在一起
Because I'm poor?
因為我沒有錢?
No, you don't understand
不，你不明白
You will never gel it
你永遠不會明白我的
Do you hate me
or is it only a game for you?
你討厭我，還是玩弄我?
Tell me
你說，說呀
Let me know
說了也好叫我明白
Don't ask anymore
不要再問
Salsali
莎莎麗
A gentle breeze
一陣陣風輕輕吹來
becomes your comfort and smile
變成了你的微笑安慰
A light rain shower
一陣陣雨飄在身邊
is refreshing as your love
一縷深情柔似水
Hello, this is Weibin
喂，我是偉彬
Salsali
莎莎麗…
You're Lin Weibin?
你叫林偉彬
And you are
你是…
Zhuzhu, I'm a singer here
我是珠珠，這兒的歌手
I know
我知道的
Laurel told me that
盧倫告訴我這些朋友中
he likes you a to: among his friends
他對你特別好
You're lucky, it's my turn to sing now
你真幸運，我要上台唱歌了
Nice to meet you
真高興見到你
That guy is
那個小兔子
with Laurel, they are gay
跟唱歌的盧倫搞同性戀的
Let's drink
來，喝酒
Weibin, Zhuzhu mm me you're here
偉彬，珠珠告訴我你在這兒
What's with you?
你怎麼了?
It's bad luck to be stuck with you
倒楣，跟你這種人在一起
We haven't done anything wrong
我們做錯了什麼?做錯了什麼?
Stop it
不要再說了
I know you feel awful
我知道你的心情
I'll find someone to keep you company
待會我找人給你解解悶
HEY
喂
Sorry to keep you waiting
對不起，久等了
What are you trying to do?
你要幹什麼?
Told you to wait for me
咱們不是講好了你在等我的嘛
Why are you so shy?
害什麼臊呢?
Damn it, it's so hot!
他媽的，熱死了
What's wrong?
怎麼了?
What's wrong? Don't stop
怎麼了?來呀
Come on, kiss me, squeeze me, hold me
來嘛，吻我捏我抱我
Just like what you were doing before
就像剛才一樣
Beat it
走開
What's wrong? Not up to it?
怎麼了，不行了?
It's not my fault
中看不中吃，這可不能怪我
Laurel has paid me already
反正盧倫已經把錢給我了
Gel out
走
I won't stay
棺材板留不住我
People say that Laurel likes guys
人家說盧倫喜歡男人
I guess so do you
你也是吧
Two guys in one bed, what else?
兩個大男人睡一張床，兔子
Damn it, you whore, get out!
他媽的，妓女，滾
Bye
拜拜
So?
怎麼樣?
I think he's just like you
你的朋友跟你一樣
Had furl?
開心吧
Weibin
偉彬
I thought you'd never show up
我以為你永遠不來看我呢
Why didn't you answer my calls?
為什麼你不接我的電話?
Have you forgotten everything?
你真的把一切都忘了
I don't wish to love, or be loved
我不要愛，也不能愛
You're lying
說謊，說謊，說謊
You forgot about us?
你忘了你曾經跟我幹過什麼
Salsali
莎莎麗
I'm here for business
這一次我是為公事而來的
You were spotted in the fashion show
last time by some clients
上一次你的時裝表演
已經受到了外界的注意
There's a better chance coming up
這一次有一個更好的表演機會
You came here to tell me this?
你來就是為了告訴我這個?
You need to work to support yourself
工作才能養活自己
Love won't get you anywhere
愛情不能當飯吃
I'll see you at the boutique tomorrow
記著明天到服裝店來，我走了
This one
就這件
Sure
好
Please come in
請進
Go try this on
拿去試穿
Sure
好
Weibin, this is yours
偉彬，這是你的衣服
Try them on
到那邊試試吧
You
你…真想不到
Are you going to be
in the fashion show too?
你也來參加這次時裝表演
You
你…
sorry
對不起
Please move over
請你讓一讓
Looks like Salsali dotes
on you a to, huh!
看來莎莎麗真的想捧你
What did you do to her?
你用什麼方法迷住她的?
You are quite a ladies'man
你真會利用女人
You gratified her in bed, is that why?
你弄得她舒服，使你有這個機會吧
Stop insulting her
你少侮辱她
You scum
你這個人
What's the matter?
怎麼回事?
Weibin
偉彬…
Are you alright?
偉彬，你怎麼了?
Please help me
快扶我回去，快扶我回去
What's with you?
你幹嘛呀
Are you alright? I'm worried
你怎麼了，把我急死了
ll hurts like hell
痛死我了
Why were you two fighting?
怎麼會這樣子的嘛
That David
他媽的大偉
He kicked me; I had to kick him back
他踢我，我非踢回他不可
I'll call the doctor
我去打電話叫醫生
No, I just need to lie down
不，我躺一會就會好了
Right, I'll get a hot towel
對了，我去弄條熟毛巾來敷一下
I've seen a neighbor who...
我看見過一個鄰居
got kicked there (00
他也是被人踢傷這兒
I think he used a hot towel
他是用熟毛巾敷好的
Take off your pants
來，把褲子脫了
Hurry, don't be shy
快，怕什麼?羞嘛
I've seen you naked; Hurry up
我都見過了，快點
It's bad
傷成這個樣子
David is (00 much
這個大偉也太狠毒了
I will never let him gel away with this
我要報復，我一定要報復
Now I'to going to
pm the hot towel over it
我要用熟毛巾敷上去
ll will be painful
你忍一忍
Laurel
盧倫
Salsali
莎莎麗
Your clothes are there, go get changed
你的衣服在那邊，去換了吧
Sure
Lin Weibin
林老兄
You got kicked in the balls
給大偉一腳踢的那個地戶
Is it working properly?
站不起來了?
How bad is it?
踢爆了沒有?
Why aren't you talking?
怎麼連話都不敢說呢?
Transformed into an eunuch now
我看變成太監了
David, look
大偉，你看
The playboy has nothing to say
風流太子不敢講話了
I don't think so
他敢講嗎?
His thing isn't very secured now
他的東西在搖搖欲墜了
David, that was quite a kick
大偉，飛毛腿真厲害
or course, I will do it again anytime
當然了，要不服氣，再來一次
What's going on?
怎麼了?
He... kicked me
他…他踢我
Salsali, it's about time
莎小姐，表演時間到了
Manager
經理
Please send someone
to take David to the hospital
請你趕快派個人送大偉到醫院去
Sure
好
Ready, everyone
各位、準備馬上出場
Mr. Lin
林先生
lean? believe that you'd give me...
我沒想到在這種緊要關頭
so much trouble just ahead of the show
你會給我搗亂
You're fired!
請你走吧
There's no place for you here
時裝界裏容不下你
Fill it up
斟酒
You're drunk
你醉了
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字?
Lulu
露露
Lulu?
露露?
Good name
是不是不穿衣服的關係?
Stop teasing me
你別開玩笑了
I think I've seen you before
我好像以前在哪兒看見過你
What's your name?
你貴姓?
You wouldn't know me: the surname's Lin
你不會認識我，我姓林
I remember
我記起了
You're the model, Lin Weibin
你是時裝模特兒林偉彬
I've seen your pictures in the magazines
我在雜誌上看見過你的照片
I was fired
不幹了，被開除了
Why? On account of a woman, is it?
為什麼?女人?
Give me the bill
結帳
One hundred and fifty
一百五十塊
Sure, it's all yours
很好，都給了你
You old bastard, who are you?
老王八蛋，你是誰?
Wait for me in the room, I'll talk to him
你到房裏去，我去跟他說
Step outside
你出來說
You have two minutes
我只給你兩分鐘時間
What do you have to say?
有什麼?話快點說
I'll call the police
if you stay over two minutes
超過兩分鐘，馬上打電話報警
We can't be together...
你不能跟我在一起
because of that old fart?
就是為了這個老頭子?
He's my foster father
我告訴你，是我的養父
Didn't imagine
you were this kind of woman!
真沒想到你是這樣的女人
Ir I can improve my lifestyle,
why the hell not ?
人活著能過得好一點，不好嗎?
You sold yourself
你出賣自己
What about you?
你呢?
I was sincere about you
我是真心對你
Love is overrated
愛情不能當飯吃
Please don't mask your true feelings
別戴假面具了
I know I've a special spot in your heart
你說難道你對我一點感情也沒有
Your time's up
你的兩分鐘已經到了
You should leave
你應該走了
You must know that I
我一定要你知道我對你…
Don't be so childish, go
別孩子氣了，走吧
Or Mr. Wang will kick you out
老王會出來趕你
Now I gel it all
我什麼都明白了
What's wrong?
你怎麼了?
It's all a lie
假的，都是假的，假的
There are plenty of fish in the sea
天下女人多的是
Why are you so stubborn?
為什麼這樣死心眼
What's so special about her?
其實她有什麼好?
What's so special about you?
你有什麼好?
Why do I like women?
對，我為什麼喜歡女人?
Why do I like that whore?
臭婊子，我為什麼喜歡她?
I shouldn't like women
我不應該喜歡女人
Laurel, you like men
盧倫，你是喜歡男人的
Tell me how
告訴我，你是怎麼喜歡男人的?
Don't insult me
你不要侮辱我
Tell me
說，你說
How do you sleep with them?
你是怎麼跟他們做愛的
Don't insult me
你不要侮辱我
Please I beg you
我求你，我求求你
If you can be with other guys...
你能跟別的男人做那種事
Why can't you do it with me?
為什麼?不能跟我?說呀
You're crazy!
你瘋了
Alright
來吧
Why am I acting like this?
我怎麼會這樣?
Anything to please you
只要使你高興，我怎麼都行
Come on then
來，我給你
You're sick! You're abnormal
噁心，你這不正常的男人
You asked me
是你要的
I don't want to see you again
我不要再見你了
Don't wanna see you ever again
我永遠不要再見你
Weibin, don't go
偉彬，不要走
Please stay, I beg you
我求求你，留下來
I'm your friend, a real friend
我是你的朋友，真正的朋友
Go to hell, why don't you kill yourself?
去你的，你去死好了
It's you!
你?
Carl I come in?
我可以進來嗎?
Why not?
沒什麼不可以
Never expected you'd be here
想不到你還會來看我
I'm not welcome?
不歡迎?
You're a model now
你已經是紅模特兒了
Salsali has her ways
莎莎麗真有辦法
Don't mention her again
不要再提她了
What? You two broke up?
怎麼?鬧翻了?
Is it because of that old marl?
是不是黃老頭有問題
Please don't talk about her
告訴你不要再提她了
You seem pale. Have a drink
你臉色不好，定定神吧
She's such a slut
賤貨，真是賤貨
Except money,
she doesn't recognize anything
除了錢，什麼都不認得
well, it's a miller of personal choice
本來嘛，人各有志
Some choose money over love
有的人要錢不要愛
Others choose love over money
有的人要愛不要錢
Remember last time I begged you to stay?
還記得我叫你留下來嗎?
Well, now I've found someone
who appreciates me
天外有天，有人此你更強
William
威廉
Du Pi, he is
杜琵，這位是…
A 'nobody'; you acted out of impulse
不相干的，你等得不耐煩了吧
Please don't get me wrong
你別弄錯了
I came here because you're my friend
我來找你是把你當朋友
Your friend?
朋友?
You've got no friends here, get out!
這裏沒有你的朋友，走
Friend'he says!
You've no friend here. Get out!
朋友?這裏沒有你的朋友，走
Gel out!
走
Weibin
偉彬
I'm your friend, a real friend
我是你的朋友，真正的朋友
Weibin...
偉彬…
Laurel
盧倫
Weibin...
偉彬…
Laurel
盧倫
Laurel...
盧倫…
Doctor
大夫
I'm sorry. We tried our best
無能為力
Laurel...
盧倫…
It's my fault
是我害死他，是我害死他的
It's because of me, I'm to blame
都怪我不好，都怪我不好
It's all... my fault!
是我…是我害死他的
Don't blame yourself
不要太責怪自己
This isn't the first time
he's attempted suicide
他自殺已經不是第一次了
He wasn't (00 happy
他從來沒有快樂過
I hate myself
我恨我自己
I can never forgive myself
我一輩子也不能原諒我自己
You cried for him, I'm glad
你為他哭，我很開心
No one has ever shed one tear for him
以前從來沒有一個人為他哭過
Go home
回去吧
Zhuzhu, come with me
珠珠，回去?
Go, hold your head up, go on...
去任何地方，抬起頭來，去…
How's Laurel?
盧倫怎麼樣?
They called me
他們打電話給我
I just got here
我匆匆忙忙的趕來
It's my fault
是我害死了他
Weibin
偉彬
I was wrong
我錯了
I've done everything wrong
我什麼都錯了
I shouldn't be wearing a mask
for a vain hope
我不應該戴著面具夢想一切
Bye
再見